{
    "subject": "resource/Hot_Rod_Circuit",
    "predicate": "ontology/recordLabel",
    "object": "resource/Triple_Crown_Records",
    "human_readable": "Hot Rod Circuit's record label is Triple Crown Records.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9009109735488892,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Hot Rod Circuit and Triple Crown Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8612464666366577,
            "question": "Who is the record label Triple Crown Records associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.852953314781189,
            "question": "Does Triple Crown Records release music by other bands besides Hot Rod Circuit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.787094235420227,
            "question": "Is Hot Rod Circuit on a record label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7490863800048828,
            "question": "Which record label has worked with Hot Rod Circuit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6829575896263123,
            "question": "Triple Crown Records is known for which type of music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6738187670707703,
            "question": "Name a band signed to Triple Crown Records."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6467127799987793,
            "question": "What record label is Hot Rod Circuit signed to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5549765825271606,
            "question": "What is the name of the record label that released Hot Rod Circuit's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3069288432598114,
            "question": "Is Hot Rod Circuit a popular band?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hot Rod Circuit's record label is Triple Crown Records.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3706_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the record label that released Hot Rod Circuit's music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3706_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What record label is Hot Rod Circuit signed to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3706_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a band signed to Triple Crown Records.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3706_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3706_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3706_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3706_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3706_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3706_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3706_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3706_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3706_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3706_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3706_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents show that Hot Rod Circuit was signed with Immortal Records, Vagrant Records, and Triple Crown Records. The statement in the triple is also partially correct, as Triple Crown Records is indeed one of their record labels."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents list \"Triple Crown Records\" among the labels associated with Hot Rod Circuit, supporting the statement that Triple Crown Records was one of their record labels."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}